<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-02-13T23:00:03-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Harang Ju’s blog</title><subtitle>PhD Candidate at UPenn
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">the Sabbath</title><link href="/blog/2020/sabbath/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="the Sabbath" /><published>2020-12-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/blog/2020/sabbath</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/2020/sabbath/">&lt;blockquote style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;
  “Remember the Sabbath day, to keep it holy. Six days you shall labor, and do all your work, but the seventh day is a Sabbath to the Lord your God. On it you shall not do any work, you, or your son, or your daughter, your male servant, or your female servant, or your livestock, or the sojourner who is within your gates. For in six days the Lord made heaven and earth, the sea, and all that is in them, and rested on the seventh day. Therefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath day and made it holy.&quot;
  &lt;div style=&quot;text-align: right;&quot;&gt;Exodus 20:8-11 ESV&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even as a Christian, it is easy to forget that the Sabbath is the fourth of the Ten Commandments, which God gave to the Israelites in the Bible. Compared to commandments like &lt;em&gt;“don’t murder”&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;“don’t steal”&lt;/em&gt;, which underlie the fabric of Western civilization, the commandment &lt;em&gt;“don’t work one day a week”&lt;/em&gt; seems trivial at best. But then why is the Sabbath one of the Ten Commandments?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is work in the first place? Back then, around a few thousand millenia BC, work probably consisted of mostly physical work—in agriculture and the like. Now, it may &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Economy_of_the_United_States_by_sector#Comparative_statistics&quot;&gt;vary&lt;/a&gt; more considerably. But no matter what the work looks like, work plays a similar role in our lives: to provide for our livelihoods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;12 Rules for Life&lt;/em&gt;, Jordan Peterson proposes an interesting evolutionary interpretation for the nature of work as described in Genesis. In Genesis, Adam and Eve eat from the tree of knowledge of good and evil, which God told them not to eat, and because of their sin, God banishes them from the garden of Eden. God says,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;
  “By the sweat of your brow
  you shall eat bread,
  until you return to the ground,
  from which you were taken&quot;
  &lt;div style=&quot;text-align: right;&quot;&gt;Genesis 3:19 ESV&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Adam and Eve eat from the fruit of the tree of the knowledge of good and evil, Peterson likens that action to Adam and Eve gaining consciousness, or at least some cognitive enhancement, so that they can now think about the future. When you think about the future, you realize the very real possibility that you may not have the means to live. Thus, you have to work to guarantee the means to your future survival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether or not Peterson’s evolutionary account is correct, you cannot ignore this existential aspect of work. That is, people work hard so that they increase the chance of their future success and avoid their demise. Personally, as a PhD student, I work in order to publish papers so that I have a better chance of getting a better job. I find myself working harder and harder to guarantee my future success. I assume that others find similar experiences in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, now that we have established the existential aspect of work, why should one regularly abstain from work? The explicit reason is that God rested and we should also rest. Exodus 20:11 says, “For in six days the Lord made heaven and earth, the sea, and all that is in them, and rested on the seventh day. Therefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath day and made it holy.” And Genesis 2:3 says, “So God blessed the seventh day and made it holy, because on it God rested from all his work that he had done in creation.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The subtext of the Ten Commandments points to an additional reason. That is that &lt;em&gt;the Sabbath is about God and not about work&lt;/em&gt;. See the three preceding commandments: (1) “You shall have no other gods before me”, (2)”You shall not make for yourself a carved image”, and (3) “You shall not take the name of the Lord your God in vain”. And immediately following these three is the Sabbath commandment, “the seventh day is a Sabbath to the Lord your God”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, why abstain from work? &lt;em&gt;Work, and our desire to quell the existential anxiety about our future, can easily become an idol that we put before God.&lt;/em&gt; Thus, the commandment is telling us to put God before work and our existential anxiety. Whether you are a Christian or not, the Sabbath highlights an important issue: are you sacrificing the things that really matter to you for things that ultimately don’t?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further, the Sabbath puts principle into practice. One of the principles behind the tithe, for example, is that your money isn’t your money; it’s God’s. By giving the tithe, you are acknowledging that fact and entrusting God with your future. The Sabbath has a similar structure: the principle is that God has ultimate power over your future and that you are entrusting God with your future over your own efforts to avoid doom. Of course, the Sabbath is not a prescription to leave everything to chance; indeed, the Sabbath is one day of rest after six days of work. Rather, it is putting into practice the principle of remembering the things that really matter to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The takeaways from this essay may be two-fold: (1) Remember what really matters to you, and (2) Act out your principles. And perhaps for Christians, a reminder to keep the Sabbath holy, a day set apart from our daily lives.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">“Remember the Sabbath day, to keep it holy. Six days you shall labor, and do all your work, but the seventh day is a Sabbath to the Lord your God. On it you shall not do any work, you, or your son, or your daughter, your male servant, or your female servant, or your livestock, or the sojourner who is within your gates. For in six days the Lord made heaven and earth, the sea, and all that is in them, and rested on the seventh day. Therefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath day and made it holy.&quot; Exodus 20:8-11 ESV</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">discovery functions</title><link href="/blog/2020/discovery-function/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="discovery functions" /><published>2020-10-21T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-10-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/blog/2020/discovery-function</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/2020/discovery-function/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  If I have seen further it is by standing on the shoulders of Giants. &lt;br /&gt;
  - Isaac Newton, 1675
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In PhD training, students are tasked with thinking about new questions to answer. That is the purpose of PhD training, to find something new and noteworthy. In my training, I would come up with a few questions that I thought would be impactful, and most of the time, someone would have already answered that question. That &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a good thing, that scientists have already thought about most of the questions that I could ask. But when my job is to find something new, it doesn’t help that I can’t think of anything new to ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The obvious answer to this problem (besides perhaps my incompetence) is that most scientists know most of the knowledge. And the questions that one can ask are dependent on what one knows. If you don’t know anything about XYZ, you can’t ask any meaningful questions about XYZ. But if you do know about XYZ, then asking questions about XYZ is not so hard. In fact, Merton, a sociologist of science, claims that &lt;em&gt;multiple discoveries&lt;/em&gt;, which are made independently and simultaneously by multiple scientists, are characteristic of scientific practice (&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1126/science.184.4137.656&quot;&gt;1974&lt;/a&gt;). Here’s a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_multiple_discoveries&quot;&gt;list&lt;/a&gt; of multiple discoveries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knowing about multiples, I then asked the question: is there a way to somehow combine our existing knowledge to find out something about a new discovery before it’s actually discovered? So, is there something like a &lt;em&gt;discovery function&lt;/em&gt; where &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;discovery = f(knowledge)&lt;/code&gt;? I was sure people have asked this question–this is the &lt;em&gt;curse of multiple discoveries&lt;/em&gt;–and people have. In fact, Prus &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Logology_(science)#Discovery&quot;&gt;discusses&lt;/a&gt; certain “laws of discovery” in 1873.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, I had the idea to use a network of Wikipedia articles, many of which have history sections with years of when the topic was discovered. I wanted to see if I could come up with a &lt;em&gt;discovery function&lt;/em&gt;. But I ended up writing a &lt;a href=&quot;http://arxiv.org/abs/2010.08381&quot;&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; on how changes in the structure of concept networks relate to theories of scientific practice by prominent 20th century philosophers of science. I enjoyed working on that project, but I made no progress on a &lt;em&gt;discovery function&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that so much of knowledge is digitized, it seems inevitable that we will come up with some kind of a &lt;em&gt;discovery function&lt;/em&gt;, if one is at all possible. Of course, there is the debate of Realism vs Nominalism, and Neil deGrasse Tyson often says that “the Universe is under no obligation to make sense to you”. So, the discovery function will likely end up being some kind of an estimation function that requires experimentation. But a &lt;em&gt;discovery function&lt;/em&gt;, or even many of them (e.g., &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-020-2855-y&quot;&gt;synthetic planning of organic compounds&lt;/a&gt;), may at least guide and facilitate the discovery process. That’d be neat.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">If I have seen further it is by standing on the shoulders of Giants. - Isaac Newton, 1675</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">dynamic neural representations</title><link href="/blog/2020/dynamic-representations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="dynamic neural representations" /><published>2020-06-17T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-06-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/blog/2020/dynamic-representations</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/2020/dynamic-representations/">&lt;p&gt;In this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-020-0653-3&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;, Dr. Bassett and I review recent studies on neural representations and on networks that model neural interactions and discuss the integration of the two topics. Featured on &lt;a href=&quot;https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-07-framework-dynamic-representations-networked-neural.html&quot;&gt;Medical Xpress&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/a-radical-new-model-of-the-brain-illuminates-its-wiring/?mbid=social_twitter&amp;amp;utm_brand=wired&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_social-type=owned&amp;amp;utm_source=twitter&quot;&gt;Wired&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key points in the article:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The brain forms representations of an ever-changing environment. The representations, therefore, are also dynamic.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The network underlying neural representations constrains how the representations change.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The structure of the brain is hierarchically modular. One way to study dynamic neural representations is to examine
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;how the brain’s network structure constrains how representations change within a brain region and&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;how changes in representations of one brain region affect the changes in another region.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that the framework provided in this review will guide my own thesis work, as well as provide others with a new perspective on dynamic neural representations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Update (July 15, 2020): Featured on &lt;a href=&quot;https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-07-framework-dynamic-representations-networked-neural.html&quot;&gt;Medical Xpress&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Update (August 17, 2020): Featured on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/a-radical-new-model-of-the-brain-illuminates-its-wiring/?mbid=social_twitter&amp;amp;utm_brand=wired&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_social-type=owned&amp;amp;utm_source=twitter&quot;&gt;Wired&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In this article, Dr. Bassett and I review recent studies on neural representations and on networks that model neural interactions and discuss the integration of the two topics. Featured on Medical Xpress and Wired.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">thoughts on the fall</title><link href="/blog/2020/forbidden-fruit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="thoughts on the fall" /><published>2020-06-16T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-06-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/blog/2020/forbidden-fruit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/2020/forbidden-fruit/">&lt;p&gt;Question: Why did God create the forbidden fruit?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thoughts: To create a perfect being with free will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dilemma: If God is omniscient yet good and perfect, why did He create the forbidden fruit, knowing that humans could, and maybe would, disobey Him?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;God probably knew that the fall would happen.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;God’s omniscience and the doctrine of predestination (e.g., Rom. 8:28, Eph. 1:5, 2 Tim. 1:9)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A mathematical case: Consider a simple model of free will, where free will implies a non-zero probability of doing anything—in this case, of eating from the tree of knowledge of good and evil.
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Assume that God wants to give them free will. So there is a non-zero probability of eating from the tree.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Then, there are two states: (A) in which Adam &amp;amp; Eve did not eat from the tree and (B) in which Adam &amp;amp; Eve ate from the tree, which is the complement of (A).&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;In (A), Adam &amp;amp; Eve live forever (since they had not eaten from the tree). If they have free will, then they will eventually eat from the tree. And they did actually eat from the tree. (Gen 3:6)&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Thus, (B) is an absorbing state. That is, given free will, Adam &amp;amp; Eve &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; to eat from the tree.
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;And if they had not eaten from the tree, can anyone say with certainty that they have free will? The question is &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Halting_problem&quot;&gt;impossible&lt;/a&gt; to answer.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;All things considered, He still put the tree there. So He probably meant to.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We know that after the fall, humans “have been sanctified through the offering of the body of Jesus Christ once for all” (Heb. 10:10). Why then did we have to fall just to be sanctified again? Why &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; just &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; put the tree there in the first place?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Ultimately, it is all for the glory of God (Psalm 19:1) and to reveal His love (1 John 4:9). But is there a more specific answer?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perhaps, &lt;em&gt;an&lt;/em&gt; answer lies in the Parable of the Prodigal Son.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Brief summary of the parable (Luke 15:11-32): There are two sons and a father. The younger son runs off with his inheritance, squanders it, and comes back to the father, hungry and miserable. The father welcomes the prodigal son and celebrates with a feast, but the older son becomes angry because he had never squandered his inheritance. The father chastises the older son, saying that he should be glad that his younger brother came back.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A common lesson from the parable is that God is welcoming us to come back to Him.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But what if the parable is actually showing us two paths of being a son:&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;(A): The older son is the Adam &amp;amp; Eve that &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; ate from the tree.
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;In Luke 15:28-29, the older son becomes angry and complains to his father, “Look, these many years I have served you, and I never disobeyed your command, yet you never gave me a young goat, that I might celebrate with my friends.”&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;The father replies, “Son, you are always with me, and all that is mine is yours.”&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;The older son never disobeyed his father; yet, he doesn’t realize, nor is grateful for, the fact that his father shared everything with him.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Maybe if Adam &amp;amp; Eve never ate from the tree, (well first, it’s questionable whether they have free will but) they would have been like the older son—always with the father yet never realizing or grateful for all that he is sharing with them.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;(B): The younger son is Adam &amp;amp; Eve that &lt;em&gt;ate&lt;/em&gt; from the tree.
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;In Luke 15:21, the younger son says, “Father, I have sinned against heaven and before you. I am no longer worthy to be called your son.”&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;But the father ignores all that and celebrates the return of his son.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Humans, as descendants of the Adam &amp;amp; Eve that &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; eat from the tree, have fallen and are “no longer to be called [His sons and daughters]”.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;But humans, like the prodigal son, can come back to the father, realizing what had been lost and eternally grateful for what had been restored.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Now presumably, the son, by &lt;em&gt;his own free will&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;eternally grateful&lt;/em&gt;, is in &lt;em&gt;perfect accordance&lt;/em&gt; with his father.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doing the impossible: creating a perfect being with free will.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;That seems like a contradiction. How does one create a being that is both perfect and has free will. &lt;em&gt;If it is perfect, then how do you know that it has free will?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;It seems that the way things played out (i.e., the fall and then Jesus’ sanctification) is the only way to achieve that sort of impossible and contradictory creation.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A “perfect being” can be likened to a slave; it is precluded from any wrongdoing. Imagine a robot that follows some simple programming—it is more a slave than an agent with free will. But how can such a being also have free will?
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Exodus 21:4-6 foreshadows this aspect of creation. It says: 4 If his master gives him a wife and she bears him sons or daughters, the wife and her children shall be her master’s, and he shall go out alone. 5 But if the slave plainly says, ‘I love my master, my wife, and my children; I will not go out free,’ 6 then his master shall bring him to God, and he shall bring him to the door or the doorpost. And his master shall bore his ear through with an awl, and he shall be his slave forever.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;The same can be said of the prodigal son.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are still in creation, sort of.&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;God technically finished creation in Genesis. But in a sense, maybe we are still in creation.
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;See 1 Corinthians 15:45. Thus it is written, “The first man Adam became a living being”; the last Adam became a life-giving spirit. 46 But it is not the spiritual that is first but the natural, and then the spiritual. 47 The first man was from the earth, a man of dust; the second man is from heaven. 48 As was the man of dust, so also are those who are of the dust, and as is the man of heaven, so also are those who are of heaven. 49 Just as we have borne the image of the man of dust, we shall also bear the image of the man of heaven.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Jesus is the embodiment of perfection by will. He paved the way from humans to become like Him.
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Ephesians 1:5. he predestined us for adoption to himself as sons through Jesus Christ, according to the purpose of his will,&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Romans 8:28. And we know that for those who love God all things work together for good, for those who are called according to his purpose. 29 For those whom he foreknew he also predestined to be conformed to the image of his Son, in order that he might be the firstborn among many brothers.&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Matthew 12:50. For whoever does the will of my Father in heaven is my brother and sister and mother.”&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Question: Why did God create the forbidden fruit?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">structure of networks underlying neural cascades</title><link href="/blog/2019/cascades/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="structure of networks underlying neural cascades" /><published>2019-05-25T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-05-25T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/blog/2019/cascades</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/2019/cascades/">&lt;p&gt;A cascade propagates longer in a neural network with stronger recurrent connections. The ongoing activity allows delayed recovery of stimuli and can act as working memory. &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/1812.09361&quot;&gt;[arXiv]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cortical neurons spike stochastically, and in networks, these spikes propagate as cascades. When distributions of cascade size and duration follow a power law, which they do (sort-of-maybe), the cascades are called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.scholarpedia.org/article/Neuronal_avalanche&quot;&gt;neuronal avalanches&lt;/a&gt; and are thought to display self-organizing criticality. While previous studies mostly use mean-field branching process theory to study cascades, we use linear dynamical systems to estimate cascading dynamics in a stochastic neuronal model and living neuronal systems. We find that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;the dominant eigenvalue of the network constrains the shape of the distribution of cascade duration,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;cycles extend cascade duration (and spikes &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; propagate cyclically in living networks),&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;highly controllable neurons (i.e., those that best control network states) best extend cascade duration, and&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;long cascades allow delayed recovery of stimulus patterns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Collectively, these results demonstrate how cascading neural networks could contribute to cognitive faculties that require persistent activation of neuronal patterns, such as working memory or attention.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A cascade propagates longer in a neural network with stronger recurrent connections. The ongoing activity allows delayed recovery of stimuli and can act as working memory. [arXiv]</summary></entry></feed>